A Guide to the Correspondence Files of Special Collections, University of Virginia Library 1931-1990s
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence (General)
  - Manuscripts Department Correspondence [ante 1990] and Patron-Use Files (Box A28-7A through A29-17T)
    - Giniger, Kenneth S. (Box A28-12C)
    - Girl Scouts (Box A28-12C)
    - Gish, Grace I. (Box A28-12C)
    - Gissing, George (Box A28-12C)
    - Gitelson, M. Leo (Box A28-12C)
    - Glasgow, Ellen 1985-1989 (Box A28-12C)
    - Glasgow, Ellen 1941-1984 (Box A28-12D)
    - Glasgow, Ellen - O. Steel Corr. (Box A28-12D)
    - Glasgow, Ellen - Literary Property Rights (Box A28-12D)
    - Goals & Objectives - Alderman Library 1986-1988 (Box A28-12E)
    - Goals & Objectives (Box A28-12E)
    - Gordon, Armistead C. (Box A28-12E)
    - Gordan, John D. (Box A28-12E)
    - Gordon, Douglas - Estate - Wind in the Willows sequel 1987-1988 (Box A28-12E)
    - Gordon, Douglas (Box A28-12E)
    - Gordon Family Papers (Box A28-12E)
    - Gordon, M.K. (Box A28-12E)
    - Gordons (Box A28-12E)
    - Gorges, Raymond & Family (Box A28-12E)
    - Gott, John K. (Box A28-12E)
    - Grace Episcopal Church (Box A28-12E)
    - Grady, Henry W. (Box A28-12E)
    - Glaspell, Susan (Box A28-12F)
    - Glass, Carter 1946-1971 (Box A28-12F)
    - Glass, Carter 1974-1988 (Box A28-12F)
    - Glass, Carter, III (Box A28-12G)
    - Glenn, Mrs. Gerrard (Box A28-12G)
    - Gloucester County (Box A28-12G)
    - Gloucestershire UK (Box A28-12G)
    - Glover, Thomas Blake (Box A28-12G)
    - Goals - Manuscripts Department (Box A28-12G)
    - Goals & Objectives (Box A28-12G)
    - Godden, Rumer (Box A28-12G)
    - Godwin, Mills E., Jr. (Box A28-12G)
    - Goeller, Mrs. Leo (Box A28-12G)
    - Goethe (Box A28-12G)
    - Goff, Frederick (Box A28-12G)
    - Gold, Jay (Box A28-12G)
    - Gold, Thomas D. (Box A28-12G)
    - Gold Rush (Box A28-12G)
    - Goldsmith, Oliver (Box A28-12G)
    - Goldwater, Walter (Box A28-12G)
    - Gooch Family (Box A28-12G)
    - Gooch Papers (Box A28-12G)
    - Gooch, Claiborne & Richard (Box A28-12G)
    - Gooch, Robert K. (Box A28-12G)
    - Gooch, William (Box A28-12G)
    - Goochland County (Box A28-12G)
    - Goode, James (Box A28-12G)
    - Goodspeeds Bookshop (Box A28-12G)
    - Goolrick, Chester (Box A28-12G)
    - Gordon, Douglas - Estate of 1988-1990 (Box A28-12G)
    - Graham, C.R. (Box A28-12H)
    - Graham Family 1989 (Box A28-12H)
    - Graham Collection (Box A28-12H)
    - Graham, Mrs. J. George R. (Box A28-12H)
    - Granberry, Bishop John Cowper (Box A28-12H)
    - Grant Application 1989 (Box A28-12H)
    - Grant, Ulysses S. (Box A28-12H)
    - Grases, Dr. Pedro (Box A28-12H)
    - Graves, Harold E. (Box A28-12H)
    - Graves, Jeremiah (Box A28-12H)
    - Graves, Joseph C. (Box A28-12H)
    - Grayson, Mrs. Jennie (Box A28-12H)
    - Green, Bennett (Box A28-12H)
    - Green, Bennett Wood - 1979 Chapter & Verse Article (Box A28-12H)
    - Green, Mrs. F.L.W. (Box A28-12H)
    - Green Family (Box A28-12H)
    - Green, Julien (Box A28-12H)
    - Green, Ralph (Box A28-12H)
    - Greene, Luther (Box A28-12H)
    - Greene, Nathanael (Box A28-12H)
    - Greer, Louise (Box A28-12H)
    - Greer, Mary Carr (Box A28-12H)
    - Gregory, E.D. (Box A28-12H)
    - Gregory, Nellie Grey Dameron (Box A28-12I)
    - Gresham (Box A28-12I)
    - Gresset, Michael (Box A28-12I)
    - Griffin Family (Box A28-12I)
    - Grimmett, Lilian D. (Mrs. William S. Grimmett) (Box A28-12I)
    - Grimsley, Ed (Box A28-12I)
    - Grinnan Collection (Box A28-12I)
    - Grinnan, Dr. St. George Tucker (Box A28-12I)
    - Grinnan Family (Box A28-12I)
    - Griswold, Rufus Wilmot (Box A28-12I)
    - Groner, Duncan G. (Box A28-12I)
    - Grove Diary (Box A28-12I)
    - Grumbach, Doris (Box A28-12I)
    - Grymes (Box A28-12I)
    - Guests to Manuscripts (Box A28-12I)
    - Gunnell, Bruce (Box A28-12I)
    - Gutenberg Bible (Box A28-12I)
    - Gwathmey, Allen T (Box A28-12I)
    - Gwathmey, Cabell (Box A28-12I)
    - Haden, Russell L. (Box A28-12B)
    - Hagood, Sen. James D. (Box A28-12B)
    - Hakluyt Society (Box A28-12B)
    - Halifax County (Box A28-12B)
    - Hall, Wilmer L. (Box A28-12B)
    - Hallam, Arthur (Box A28-12B)
    - Halle, Louis J. (Box A28-12B)
    - Halpine, Charles (Box A28-12B)
    - Halsey, Adm. (Box A28-12B)
    - Hamberger, William L. (see also MSS #9714) (Box A28-12B)
    - Hamer, Phillip - Guide to Manuscript Collections (Box A28-12B)
    - Hamilton, Alexander (Box A28-12B)
    - Hamilton, Charles (Box A28-12B)
    - Hamilton, Mary (Box A28-12B)
    - Hammond, George (Box A28-12B)
    - Hammond, L.M. (Box A28-12B)
    - Hamond Papers (Box A28-12B)
    - Hamond, Sir Andrew Snape (Box A28-12B)
    - Hampden-Sidney College (Box A28-12B)
    - Hampton, Wade (Box A28-12C)
    - Hanberry, James (Box A28-12C)
    - Hancock, John W. (Box A28-12C)
    - Hancock, W. Scott - Journal (Box A28-12J)
    - Handy, Edward C.S. (Box A28-12J)
    - Hanes, Leigh (Box A28-12J)
    - Hanes, Thomas Andrews (Box A28-12J)
    - Hanover County Virginia (Box A28-12J)
    - Hanover County Tax Book (Box A28-12J)
    - Happel, Ralph (Box A28-12J)
    - Harding, Walter (Box A28-12J)
    - Hardy, Thomas (Box A28-12J)
    - Hariot (Box A28-12J)
    - Harold, E.B. 1988 (Box A28-12J)
    - Harold, Mrs. Edward B. (Box A28-12J)
    - Harkrader, Charles J. (Box A28-12J)
    - Harrigan, Anthony (Box A28-12J)
    - Harris, Doris (Box A28-12J)
    - Harris Family (Box A28-12J)
    - Harris, Harry (Box A28-12J)
    - Harris, Joel Chandler (Box A28-12J)
    - Harrison, Albertis S. (Box A28-12J)
    - Harrison, Burr P. (Box A28-12J)
    - Harrison, Fairfax - Mr. & Mrs. (Hetty Cary Harrison) (Box A28-12J)
    - Harrison Family (Box A28-12J)
    - Harrison, Francis Burton (Box A28-12J)
    - Harrison, Gessner (Box A28-12J)
    - Hart, Andrew (Box A28-12J)
    - Hart Family (Box A28-12J)
    - Hart, James (Box A28-12J)
    - Harte, Bret (Box A28-12J)
    - Hawthorne, Nathaniel (Box A28-12J)
    - Harvard University (Box A28-12K)
    - Harwell, Richard B. 1954-1956 (Box A28-12K)
    - Haushalter, Walter M. (Box A28-12K)
    - Hawes Family (Box A28-12K)
    - Hawkes, John - Mr. & Mrs. (Sophie T. Hawkes) (Box A28-12K)
    - Hawthorne, Nathaniel (Box A28-12K)
    - Hay, Mary Oakley (Box A28-12K)
    - Hay, T.R. (see also Magruder, John) (Box A28-12K)
    - Haydn, Joseph (Box A28-12K)
    - Hayes, Rutherford B. (Box A28-12K)
    - Hazelgrove (Box A28-12K)
    - Heaney, Howell J. (see also Dickens, Charles) (Box A28-12K)
    - Hearn, Lafcadio (Box A28-12K)
    - Heaton, H. Thayer (Box A28-12K)
    - Hedges, Dr. Halstead S. (Box A28-12L)
    - H.E.W. Special Fund (Box A28-12L)
    - Heard, John Theodore (Box A28-12L)
    - Heflin, Aubrey (Box A28-12L)
    - Heite, Edward F. (Box A28-12L)
    - Hemingway, Ernest (Box A28-12L)
    - Hemphill, John, II 1956-1960 (Box A28-12L)
    - Hemphill, W. Edwin 1950-1955 (Box A28-12L)
    - Hench, Atcheson L. (Box A28-12L)
    - Hench Catalogue (Box A28-12M)
    - Hench, Philip (Box A28-12M)
    - Hench - Yellow Fever (Box A28-12M)
    - Hench - Yellow Fever - Carroll (Box A28-12M)
    - Henkel (Box A28-12M)
    - Henkel Family (Box A28-12M)
    - Henkel Family Papers & Press (Box A28-12M)
    - Henry (John) Map of Virginia (Box A28-12M)
    - Henry, Joseph (Box A28-12M)
    - Henry, O. (Box A28-12M)
    - Henry, Patrick (Box A28-12M)
    - Herbert, Henry William (Box A28-12M)
    - Hereford, Frank L. (Box A28-12M)
    - Herndon, Dr. Brodie S. (Box A28-12M)
    - Herndon Family (Box A28-12M)
    - Herndon, John W. (Box A28-12M)
    - Herrick, Robert (Box A28-12M)
    - Herringman, Henry (Box A28-12M)
    - Heth Papers (Box A28-12M)
    - Heth-Selden Papers (Box A28-12N)
    - Hey, Colin G. (Box A28-12N)
    - Hiden, Mrs. Philip W. (Box A28-12N)
    - Higginbotham, David (Box A28-12N)
    - Higginbottom, Samuel (Box A28-12N)
    - Hildreth, William S. (Box A28-12N)
    - Hill, Gen. A.P. (Box A28-12N)
    - Hill, Archibald A. (Box A28-12N)
    - Hilliard & Gray (Box A28-12N)
    - Hilldrup Manuscript (Box A28-12N)
    - Hilton, James (Box A28-12N)
    - Hinman, Charlton (Box A28-12N)
    - Hirsch, Rudolf (Box A28-12N)
    - Historic Green Springs, Inc. (Box A28-12N)
    - Historical Collections - Annual Reports (Box A28-12N)
    - Historical Societies (Box A28-12N)
    - History Club - University of Virginia (Box A28-12N)
    - Hite, Mrs. Edgar L. (Box A28-12N)
    - Hitler (Box A28-12N)
    - Hobbes (Box A28-12N)
    - Hobbs, William H. (Box A28-12N)
    - Hobson, Fanny (Box A28-12N)
    - Hoes, Laurence G. (Box A28-12N)
    - Hogan, J.R. (Box A28-12O)
    - Hoge, William A. (Box A28-12O)
    - Hogshead, Mrs. Richard (Box A28-12O)
    - Hohner, Robert A. (Box A28-12O)
    - Holladay Family (Box A28-12O)
    - Holliday, Frederick William (Box A28-12O)
    - Holland, Dr. Charlton G. (Box A28-12O)
    - Holmes, George Frederick (Box A28-12O)
    - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (Box A28-12O)
    - Holsinger Studio (MSS #9862) (Box A28-12O)
    - Holsinger Studio Collection (Box A28-12O)
    - Holt, Stephen Philip (Box A28-12O)
    - Hooe and Harrison (Box A28-12O)
    - Hook, James Lewis (Box A28-12O)
    - Hook, John, material (Box A28-12O)
    - Hoover, Herbert (Box A28-12O)
    - Horn, Andrew H. (Box A28-12P)
    - Horn Papers (Box A28-12P)
    - Horn, Stanley F. (Box A28-12P)
    - Horner, David L., III (Box A28-12P)
    - Horner Manuscripts (MSS #379) (Box A28-12P)
    - Hostick, King V. (Box A28-12P)
    - Hotchkiss, Jed 1938-1960 (Box A28-12P)
    - Hough, Emerson (Box A28-12P)
    - Houghton, Herbert (Box A28-12P)
    - House, Edward (Box A28-12P)
    - House Bill #67 - Public Records Act, 1976 (Box A28-12P)
    - Housing Requests - University of Virginia (Box A28-12P)
    - Housman, A.E. (Box A28-12P)
    - Houston, David F. (Box A28-12P)
    - Houston, Sam (Box A28-12P)
    - Houstoun (Box A28-12P)
    - Howard, Carter Eugene (Box A28-12P)
    - Howell, Morton Boyte (Box A28-12P)
    - Howells, William Dean (Box A28-12P)
    - Hoxton (Box A28-12P)
    - Hoy, Peter 1989 (Box A28-12P)
    - Hubard Family Manuscripts (Box A28-12P)
    - Howe, George L. (Box A28-12Q)
    - Howes, Wright (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hroswithe Club (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hubbard, Fred C. (see also Presses, Private) (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hubbell (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hudson Bay Record Society (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hudson, W.H. (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hughes, Thomas P. (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hugo, Harold (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hummel (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hunley (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hunt Botanical Library (Box A28-12Q)
    - Huntington (Henry E.) Library and Art Gallery) (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hutcheson, Francis (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hutchins, John S. (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hutchinson, C.A. (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hutchison, Elizabeth M. (Box A28-12Q)
    - Huttner, Elizabeth Stege (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hyde, Donald (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hydrometer (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hynan, Patrick (Box A28-12Q)
    - Hubbell (Box A28-12R)
    - Huger, Benjamin (Box A28-12R)
    - Hugo, Harold (Box A28-12R)
    - Harold Hugo Project - Jefferson Drawing for the Rotunda (Box A28-12R)
    - Hulbert, Judge Henry Schoolcraft (Box A28-12R)
    - Humboldt, Alexander von (Box A28-12R)
    - Hummel (Box A28-12R)
    - Humphreys, Milton Wyllie (Box A28-12R)
    - Hundley, Mrs. Peyton (see also Brydon, G.) (Box A28-12R)
    - Huneker (Box A28-12R)
    - Hunt Family (Box A28-12R)
    - Hunt, Henry B., Jr. (Box A28-12R)
    - Hunt, Leigh - and Portrait (Box A28-12R)
    - Hunt, Mrs. Roy (Box A28-12R)
    - Hunter, Dard (see also Imprimature) (Box A28-12S)
    - Hunter, James (Box A28-12S)
    - Hunter, John H. (Box A28-12S)
    - Hunter, Thomas Lomax (Box A28-12S)
    - Hunter, R.M.T. (Box A28-12S)
    - Hunter-Garnett Papers (Box A28-12S)
    - Huntington (Henry E.) Library and Art Gallery (Box A28-12S)
    - Hunton, Eppa (Box A28-12S)
    - Hurd, Charles (Box A28-12S)
    - Hurt (see also Stone Printing & Manufacturing) (Box A28-12S)
    - Hurt Family (Box A28-12S)
    - Hutcheson, Joseph C. (Box A28-12S)
    - Hutchinson, C.A. (Box A28-12S)
    - Hutchinson, Helen (Box A28-12S)
    - Hutchinson Papers (Box A28-12S)
    - Hutter, C.S., Jr. / Edwin C. Hutter (Box A28-12S)
    - Huxley, Aldous (Box A28-12S)
    - Hyde, Donald (Box A28-12S)
    - H misc. (Box A28-12T)
    - I misc. 1930-1988 (Box A28-12T)
    - Imboden Papers (Box A28-12T)
    - Imprimatur (Box A28-12T)
    - Imprints (Box A28-12T)
    - Incunabula (Box A28-12T)
    - Index - English NUCMC (Box A28-12T)
    - Indexing (Box A28-12T)
    - India (Box A28-12T)
    - Indiana (Box A28-12T)
    - Indians (Box A28-12T)
    - Industrial History Society (Box A28-12T)
    - Ingles, John (Box A28-12T)
    - Inglesias, Santiago (Box A28-12T)
    - Ingram, John Henry (Box A28-12T)
    - Institute of Early American History and Culture (Box A28-13A)
    - Institute of Historical Research (Box A28-13A)
    - Instituto Panamericano (see also Spanish American) (Box A28-13A)
    - Insurance 1965-1979 (Box A28-13A)
    - Insurance 1984 (Box A28-13A)
    - Insurance - Collections 1981-1984 (Box A28-13A)
    - Insurance - State Policy Review 1985 (Box A28-13A)
    - Insurance for our collections (1987- ) (Box A28-13A)
    - Insurance - General University of Virginia (Box A28-13A)
    - Insurance Schedule - Retired (Box A28-13A)
    - Insurance 1939-1964 (Box A28-13B)
    - Insurance Policy & Endorsements 1972 Mar 9-1975 Mar 9 (Box A28-13B)
    - Insurance - Rare Books (Box A28-13B)
    - Interlibrary Loan (Box A28-13B)
    - Internships (Box A28-13B)
    - Internships Program (Box A28-13B)
    - International Congress on Archives (Box A28-13B)
    - Invoices (Box A28-13B)
    - Invoices - B MSS Fund (Box A28-13B)
    - Irvine, Robert Tate (Box A28-13B)
    - Irving, Washington 1970-1984 (Box A28-13B)
    - Irving, Washington 1989 (Box A28-13B)
    - Ivy Creek Foundation 1988-1989 (Box A28-13B)
    - Irving, Washington 1962-1969 (Box A28-13C)
    - J misc. 1930-1984) (Box A28-13C)
    - J misc. 1985-1989 (Box A28-13D)
    - Jackson, Andrew (Box A28-13D)
    - Jackson, Luther P. (Box A28-13D)
    - Jackson, Stonewall (Box A28-13D)
    - Jackson, Stuart W. 1955-1957 (Box A28-13D)
    - Jackson, W.A. (Box A28-13D)
    - Jaffe, Louis I. (see also J misc.) (Box A28-13D)
    - James Family (Box A28-13D)
    - James, Henry (Box A28-13D)
    - James, Henry - C.W. Barrett / Leon Edel (Box A28-13D)
    - Jamestown (Box A28-13D)
    - Jamestown Festival - Exhibits (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - Hemphill, John 1957 (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival 1957 (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - Jefferson Day (see also Loans - Manuscripts) (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - Gift 1957 (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - Library of Congress 1957 (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - McGregor Publications 1957 (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - Miscellaneous (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - Overseas Guests & Participation 1954-1957 (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - Publications Committee 1957 (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - Publicity 1957 (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Island - Committee (Box A28-13F)
    - Jamestown Festival - University of Virginia Participation 1957 (Box A28-13G)
    - Japan (Box A28-13G)
    - Jay, John (Box A28-13G)
    - Jefferson, Isaac (Box A28-13G)
    - Jefferson, Martha (Box A28-13G)
    - Jefferson, Peter (Box A28-13G)
    - Jefferson, Thomas 1979-1984 (Box A28-13G)
    - Jefferson, Thomas 1971-1977 (Box A28-13H)
    - Jefferson - Account Books 1985-1986 (Box A28-13H)
    - Jefferson - Account Book 1989 (Box A28-13H)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Biographies (Box A28-13H)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Books (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Library (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Cabell letters (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Calendar 1964-1977 (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Calendar 1981-1985 (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Calendar 1941-1950 (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Calendar - Suppl[ement] - estimate of printing (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Cannons of Conduct (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - 1828 Catalogue of the University of Virginia Library (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Ceracchi (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Checklist - Boyd, Julian P. (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Checklist - Form Letters & Replies (alphabetical) (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Checklist - General (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Chicago Jubilee (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Christmas Cards (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Cipher Codes (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson - Ciphers 1987-1989 (Box A28-13I)
    - Jefferson, Thomas 1941-1970 (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Account Books (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Agriculture (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Ancestry (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Architecture 1930-1960 (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Autographs (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Award (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Bedford County (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Bennett Henderson Estate (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Bible (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Bibliography (Box A28-13J)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Ciphers (Box A28-13K)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Clippings (Box A28-13K)
    - Jefferson - Cosway (Box A28-13K)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Documents (Box A28-13K)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Drawings 1974-1977 (Box A28-13K)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Drawings 1978 Apr-1984 (Box A28-13K)
    - Jefferson - Papers of Thomas Jefferson - Bullock (Box A28-13L)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Papers of 1951-1972 (Box A28-13L)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Papers of - Princeton University 1988-1989 (Box A28-13L)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Music (1988- ) (Box A28-13L)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Drawings 1988-1989 (Box A28-13L)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Drawings 1949-1971 (Box A28-14S)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Drawings 1972-1973 (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Drawings 1985 (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Drawings 1987 (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Drawings - Carlitz Lot (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson - Du Moulin (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson - Dunglison (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Education (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson - Engravings Notes (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Engravings of (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson - Eppes (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson - Facsimiles (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Morris Plan Bank Facsimile (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson - Family Genealogy (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Family manuscripts (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Farm Book (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Fellowships (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Garden Books (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Genealogy (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Iconography (Box A28-15A)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Inventions (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Law (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson - Lawyers (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson - Letters Missing (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Letters Obtained 1950-1966 (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Letters Not Obtained 1946-1954 (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Letters Not Obtained 1956-1965 (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Letters Not Obtained (1968- ) (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson - Letters - Tucker-Coleman (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Letters (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson - Letters (Box A28-13M)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Library (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Library of Congress (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Collection - Library of Congress (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Burke (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Huntington Library (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Kean, Jefferson Randolph (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Massachusetts Historical Society (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - McGregor Collections (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Medal (MSS #38-592) (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Missouri Historical Society (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Manuscripts in Morgan Library (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - National Archives (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Taylor, Olivia (see also Kirk...) (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Union List of Papers at University of Virginia (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - University of Texas Library (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Memorial Foundation (Box A28-13N)
    - Jefferson, Thomas 1986-1989 (Box A28-13O)
    - Jefferson - Notes - Peden (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Pen (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Peyton (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson - Philosophy (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Philosophy of Jesus (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson - Phi Kappa Alpha (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Pictures (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson on Plato (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson - Poet (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Polygraph (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson - Poplar Forest (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson - Portaits (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Prayer Book (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Relics (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Religion (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson - Rockfish Gap Commission Report (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - St. Memin Engraving (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Scandals (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Science (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson & Science Exhibition 1981 (Box A28-13P)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Memorial Foundation 1951 (Box A28-13Q)
    - Jefferson - Manuscripts - Monticello (Box A28-13Q)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Music (Box A28-13Q)
    - Jefferson - Nail Factory (Box A28-13Q)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - New Testament (Box A28-13Q)
    - Jefferson - Notes on Virginia - Clemons (Box A28-13Q)
    - Jefferson - Notes on Virginia - Verner (Box A28-13Q)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Notes on Virginia (Box A28-13Q)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Scrapbooks (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Seal (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Slaves (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Society (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson - Stockdale Correspondence (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Tombstone (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Violins (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Will (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson Wine Grape Growers Society 1986-1988 (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Wines & Other Spirits (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Writings of (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Miscellaneous (Box A28-13R)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Nugent Code (Box A28-13R)
    - Jeffress, Robert M. (Box A28-13R)
    - Jenner, Edward (Box A28-13R)
    - Jennings, John Melville (Box A28-13R)
    - Jervis, John B. (Box A28-13R)
    - Jesuit Relations (Box A28-13R)
    - Jewett, Sarah Orne (Box A28-13R)
    - Job Descriptions - MSS Dept. - Old (Box A28-13R)
    - Johns, Mrs. Frank S. (Box A28-13R)
    - Johns, Jay W. (Box A28-13R)
    - Johnson, Andrew (Box A28-13R)
    - Johnson, Bradley T. (Box A28-13R)
    - Johnson, Evans (Box A28-13R)
    - Johnson, H.P. (Box A28-13R)
    - Johnson, Louis Arthur (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnston, Mary (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnson, Meredith (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnson, Mildred (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnson, Sam (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnson, Samuel (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnson, Thomas Cary (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnson, Mrs. T. Cary (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnson, Walter (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnston, Clem D., Library (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnston, James Ambler (Box A28-13S)
    - Johnston, Mary 1946-1984 (Box A28-13T)
    - Johnston, Zachariah (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones, Mrs. A. Waldo (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones Commission Rules (Box A28-13T)